Oluwaseun Esther Agboola

Customer Engagement and Success

Stockholm, Sweden | +46768147371 | <u>ogeariyo@gmail.com</u> | linkedin.com/in/oluwaseun-agboola-762429102

Objective

I am a highly skilled and motivated customer engagement and success manager with over 4 years of experience in process and service management in the financial business transformation environment. I have a consultative approach to working with clients and a keen focus on customer satisfaction through high-level and tactical communication, teamwork, and timely delivery. I am excited to join a high-growth company where I can expand and grow my career while making a meaningful impact.

Experience

Globus Bank | Team Lead Customer Engagement and Customer Service Manager June 2020 – Feb 2022

- Managed multiple client relationships.
- Created and implemented a training program for new customer service representatives resulting in a reduction in training time.
- Trained customer service team members on product knowledge and customer service best practices.
- Acted as a liaison between customers and management, providing timely feedback and updates.
- Recognized customer needs and provided personalized solutions, resulting in increased customer loyalty and satisfaction.
- Planned internal resources and customer meetings with thorough documentation and rigorous follow-up.
- Fraud Investigations, Data Integrity management, Regulatory Compliance, Financial Transactions, ATM Management and reconciliation, Vault Management, Branch Operations Supervision, Customer queries, Customer Onboarding.

First Bank of Nigeria | Customer Experience and Success Manager Feb 2017 - June 2020

- Implemented customer service strategies, improved service quality and streamlined processes in the organization.
- Coordinated with the team to provide timely customer support which improved customer satisfaction
- Helped streamline customer service processes thereby reducing response times.
- Identified appropriate responses and strategies for unique customer cases to solve customer issues as quickly as possible.
- Trained and mentored new customer service team members to ensure a high level of customer service.
- Back Office Administrator, Non-Financial Transaction Officer, Financial Transaction Officer, Fraud Investigations, International Money Transfer, ATM Management.

National Youth Service Corps (NYSC) | Government Secondary School, Afikpo Oct 2015 – Oct 2016

Mandatory service to the nation in the education sector.

Education

Eductus, Sollentuna (Svenska för Invandrare) | Oct 2023 – Jul 2024

SFI C & SFI D

Lexicon Yrkesutbildning, Växjö | Oct 2022 - Jun 2023

Java Full Stack System Developer: Java, Spring Boot, RESTful Webservices, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, etc.

Udemy & FutureLearn | Feb 2022 - Oct 2022

UI/UX Design: Basics of designing, Wireframing, Prototyping, User Research, UI Design, etc.

Covenant University, Nigeria | Second Class: Upper Division 2015

B.Eng Computer Engineering

Skills & Abilities

- Team Player
- Rapid and Adaptive
- Effective Cross Functional Communication
- Solutions Oriented Professional
- High Achiever

Language

English: Mother Tongue

Swedish: Work knowledge